

UMUT KAAN ÖZDEMIR

Computer Scientist, Game Developer

- y01cu.github.io
- @ umutaan50@gmail.com
- in umut-kaan-özdemir-501032203
- v01cu
- **J** +905514259473

Ankara, Türkive

ABOUT ME

I am a committed Computer Scientist and Game Developer with nearly three years of experience. My latest project, a game now available on Google Play, highlights my skills in creating engaging digital experiences.

A lifelong gamer, I have the potential to bring both passion and technical expertise to the table. I am excited about the opportunity to collaborate with Company X's team, contributing to innovative projects and driving the future of gaming and interactive techonologies.

LANGUAGES

Turkish: Native

English: Advanced / C1

REFERENCES

Öner Önçer - Onivo Games: Owner

- in oner-oncer-413391161
- ✓ oneroncer@gmail.com

Filiz Koçoğlu - Doctoral Thesis Writer

- in filiz-koçoğlu-2349ab121

Ridvan Bal - Mayadem: Developer

- in ridvan-bal-2b144862
- bal.rdvn@gmail.com

TECH STACK

Unity: VR/Mobile/PC



WebGL Git

GLSL

Blender

EXPERIENCE

Indie Game Developer - Onivo Games

i 10.2023 - Still

- Ankara, Türkiye (Remote)
- I have developed our arcade idle mobile game in our two people team. Handled Firebase Analytics, Facebook Ads, Google Admob, Google IAP, In app update. Used navmesh system for helper agents. Implemented a proper data save system and made the game easily scalable for future development.
- Link of the game -> **\$** Gained 540 user acquisition in two weeks.

Unity Developer - Doctoral Thesis

1 09.2022 - Still

- Ankara, Türkiye (Remote)
- Updated ALCO-VR project for the current state of VR for a doctoral thesis. Changed it's language and added a Turkish equivalent "meyhane" scene. Implementing the project in Meta Quest 3 right now.

Internship - Mayadem | •



1 08.2022 - 09.2022

- Ankara, Türkiye (Remote)
- Developed a 2D puzzle platformer game using Unity Engine. Implemented a relatively complex player controller that can climb, inventory system. Used custom animation rigging and sprite shapes.

Internship - Enoks | 🌐



= 07.2021 - 08 2021

- Ankara, Türkiye (In-Office)
- Updated their, reporting system software that had a connection with excel sheet. Used MSSQL with Visual Studio.

EDUCATION

Bachelor's degree, Computer. Eng. | Gazi University, Eng. Fac.

2019 - 2023

Ankara, Türkiye

PROJECTS

All of My Projects | •



• Including 2D, 3D games, my graduation project, my Unity tools, my jam games, and all other projects of mine can be found in my portfolio website. More than 20 projects are sorted considering time spent to them